All right.
A. Whole the
off.
All.
Off.
The new.
Age. I hate.
Bad.
Rap.
But the old girl. With knowledge.
Of the. All right
a. Oh. Oh right oh yea.
I laugh laugh laugh laugh at the power
I. Want to take a break
a good. Evil woman
waiting for. The advice.
I got for you all of it's been all
right. I'm going to make the time of my
life and I And speaking of time I have.
A fourteen carat seventeen year old
time. I met only right because a
man I'm getting it through is
a fourteen carat seventeen jewel
case you. Did long ago I thought
I had all that wonderful Now
that's good I. Like that's what
I was. Requesting greenside gratis.
To my friend Christopher Cross.
In token of twenty five years as
a fake or service. J.J.
I hope God. Nineteen zero
nine nineteen thirty four.
The quest. The eight. I
hardly know what to say J.J.
. They say. It's beautiful. And I never
expected on
a watch like this and I was there
I. Well all I can say is that
we've got the best boss in
New York I've. Got the place
and the I.A.E.A.
The Ballo the maps the layout
a narrow the regulation don't like.
That. Thank you Chris. Thank you my old
friend that would help but I think I was
well before I go Well I don't usually see
a joy and pride made special for
me our first child I told the.
British. Thank.
You not superstitious are you. Not
sure and I. Said I don't really have
a good idea because I've got to go
everything is trying to change all the
things are you on the coming like
Monday morning and I know all the right
that was. The idea. That you know the
left and the is right and the old
wasn't true either that's right and I.
Like that ELEANOR BELL
knock knock company.
Six.
Can hold and then tell me. Why if.
The boss is that big now. I know
your life I'll be all right
a lot written I'm.
Nothing like the smell of spring which
way to go and I guess I'll take the side
that way it's going to Brooklyn
a little because. You you haven't
got an umbrella think any of
us are not out of your way I don't mind
walking you know right there spring if. I
followed rock.
Never mind I guess and I'm sure you want
out of some way so I don't mind waiting I
feel kind of lonely it's nice. JOLLY.
Useful if you do something thank
you and maybe it sucks either way.
I wonder what it's like why Frisch.
Well to be to be loved by like.
You know nobody ever looked like that not
even when I was. VERY young when I was
being just never plan out for. A run
dreaming when I was young I wanted to be an
artist you know I dreamt I was
going to be a great painter. I'm
a guy here and we're still friends ever
since I was one way to. You know sometimes
wonder Rick that I don't live there and I
want to do it myself What is the moment
I'm on seem like if I
was. A nice person Good
night Charlie I see tomorrow night.
To stop running after our fellow which
way is the least that's a way from
a quarter past the hour of August I go
there I guess I got turned around the
streets are all mixed up the age at.
The head. I go call
a place but the only. Oh
. Oh.
But they go to that wreck. Right I don't
know I didn't see space because fifteen
dollars I didn't leave it all I had began
pushing me around and this John Brennan
I'm not in the lead right off so he was
right there I couldn't help me got up and
read. What we have to wait for the officer
I want to get my name in the newspaper to
you with the news but sure we'll have to
go to the station house make
a complaint and every time to make an
arrest and take it out a week so it's
a nuisance. But you take me home my yes.
Well if you think that. Well.
Come up but I share my apartment with
another girl you know. The night Thanks for
having. Gone to I don't
want to cup of coffee when
the right.
Hello I. Like to know you missed. I do.
Is seen John. Since he left. To go.
And I can stand
a great. Oh come on to. Make
my mom say. You know since I first saw
you I was wondering which name was.
Really. Catherine. My
friend. Plenty of and call you. Chris.
As they tease me about it. I don't mind.
Right you're looking at.
I think. The better the.
Body.
Responds. To Yes as I had in the. Kitty.
Well look Kitty. Says I bought
it at your father about.
I don't think so. But.
I like that you know. What I want to say
right. Here in the lawn of the streets
elated. I was coming home
from work. Work this late.
What do you do.
You're an actress. Now that you
know all about me. What do you do
I. What you see I don't
tell. We're going to.
Greenwich Village and. I'm each
one going to kill. You not right.
If I paid. I think I took you for
a cashier. You know. They charge I
picture the call. They called. These days
that it was
a great Frenchman. I like
don't have. Your blood. Deep
down. You can't put any price on
masterpieces like that that we're.
Well whatever you can afford to pay for.
You know what Chris I. Know next time I
look you know. I don't so. Well not
know you. Know I know that.
Pageant someplace like that
tell I don't know much about Penny I bet
you get as much for your pictures in fact
as those Frenchmen get right here in New
York you never appreciated in your own
country. That that's one way of looking
at it. But you know what I paint I don't
think of money I just pay for fun. Yes
I think it's the most fun I know.
I wish I had all the time to
pay attention that. Well you.
Know. Business takes
a lot of time I wonder when you get all
that money. What play you acting and.
Which one at what time.
It's only ten best to. Good then.
So you want it in. The can
I feel good and good and
I'm sure if you give me
a telephone and I haven't got out of me
I write you that it read going to Ikea
kitty who is Johnny the you right there
but I just want us to broadcast that.
Come the show he's
a fellow I know he's the No I'd like
then you know the girl I love with and I
goodnight Kitty.
The
and. The OR or
the
yes that.
Well this is
a pleasure I didn't expect to see you
Charlie but Chris you asked me. Why
I have it so that is good
to see you anyway. That was
a swell party last night I was
a child they had what I would
go home after midnight was let.
You know I have been to bed yet you
haven't I guess and I was told that I was
a challenge. And oh I've got to do the
dishes spread out you know my child I did NO
NO NO reading.
Did you buy this great Scott now that
isn't painting that's mud that my
photographer who is. The late
departed home you know wakes from
a tech there sat in Hague and.
Said that the reason better
than that. And out about
it. You know why Yeah
after he was down at least or. Get
them to say one. Day The body
was wrong. But yet still there.
Thank you. Longing for it.
I. Didn't want to spend years insurance
money associate rented out sparrow.
Twenty four dollars
a week well I was trying to save money
to buy pension so I moved and. She
was sweet but I wouldn't
know mouth. And the.
Things. Well stuff.
Right. There of the heart which
actually what I did today like you know
what. The you know.
When to find
a flower and I say. The You mean you see
this when you look at. The
desires of the see that. You see
when I look at that flower I see
some of. The think that I have.
I'm sorry I doubt it but you know.
All I. Can. Stuff.
The view.
The right.
As you get those lazy legs of the
couch very quiet. Can't you do
any better as
a rat that's all you think about lazy
lay some one else think about. If
you want more heat and there's
a problem and you'll have to call it
jello. How come you're golden I'm
a baby Oh the talking about that it ain't
no talking about Saturday night I'm
talking about this. That's like
a schoolboy trying to make
a day with the robin and Craig I want the
funny you don't have to be my father it
was the old fellow came
to my rescue is that
a no right my hero no kidding me you are
too tight remember anything I had all the
coffee gone the wrong direction
to pick you up if you don't got
a better then the payday. He's
rich and famous and very charming.
Like you well Jessica you know but
a crap game all I needed was the bug and
wanted to show up with Dean that's all I
had that you kept me waiting two hours
in the rain and then you gave me
a dirty look I didn't give you
a dirty look listen any girl
waits two hours in the rain for
a guy is going to give him
a dirty look. Trouble with your
baby is you have no imagination.
What expect me to do I get back to that
use your brain. But just think this child
goes crazy about this is the set up isn't
that big money is. That picture from.
My brain that dreaded is
a little cap and this is right in your lap
you don't have to call what's his name
and get him basically. Good feel about
right they don't have the right tend to
take money and oh man like that. I can't
say if the kind of lazy leg I thought
was in the big dog without my brain's
ability you know you're going to have money
to make capital the boys at the Acme
garage. Does that I can put up
the money oh three or four.
Cats talking about chicken feed you use
your imagination. To get an interest in
a business like that. To squeeze out
your life. Then your enemies Hebrews the
pipe dreams you hair what if I said that I
can get fifty or one hundred perhaps but
I can't get the kind of money you're
talking about I would never tell. Johnny
get it where you go is what I would
be wasting my time I just don't.
I don't know I'm crazy about you oh yes
you do know about the proposition.
You don't have to have your child for much
notice we're going to these an apartment
company run like become another
I don't like this. Well as
a leg. I come into my own
apartment from my face I
just go get it done and I go about my staff
looking at my fiance How do you spell
that word whether they're like
a. Sheep is that the or the rather the
general idea that sadly sadly Well I don't
mind if you want this but. The you can.
If you mean by their thing you know Johnny
Yeah I know Johnny All right the doctor
that gave you seem to worry
more about it than I do.
You forty five dollar model Roger
let me have a Brady that it be
a problem that the two modeling
good. I have been know. I ate
like a dork. Causing them
a comeback I swear I'll quit
modeling. Why don't you
go back to work that figure he was
a darn lady. So do you you
think. My God. Not me honey
wings
a long time ago. When you got farther
than. You never could get to
work on time after the mess
that Johnny. I was happy to.
Get happened to you I'm crazy a man to
push you around the way I would with
a cat around even trying. To get
a value was. Rather young and.
That's where the the.
The
poor the rat.
The are. The I'm.
The you you you. The are
really. Problems just like I.
Look there's
a pair of them up that they're
building that nest. They
were still in there. And when I was. Four
years. I feel I could get myself.
Sold anything. But
a Japan. Type like to what can I bring my
your apartment I'm afraid my girlfriend
wouldn't. Take the paint
a picture. Sometimes
a day sometimes you can tell it has
to go kind of a new paint to grab
a feeling. You know that's the feeling
when I you take me that you were taught me
how to draw so I just put
a line around what I feel when I look in
the yeah. It's like. It's like owning
a lot like you know. You know. First you
see someone and it keeps growing and.
You can't think of anyone else and.
The way I look at things that. Every
painting if it's any good is
a lovely. I never heard anyone. Talk
this way. To keep. Everything but.
I'm sorry keeping things bottled
up too Chris. Has an agenda
you probably guessed it I'm broke in
the mill and I can't pay my rent.
Well how much is about to get
it I shouldn't have told you.
How did. I couldn't take
anything no yes I mean. I've
never taken money and I'm not
going and I'm not going to. I
couldn't pay you back. Maybe I could.
If you problematic apartment and I have
a place to live in. My poetry.
As
a matter. That you want
to paint my picture. You
.
Tell me. You know I'm not
the kind of girl. You
know what you said about meeting someone.
High begin to like. And you can't think
about anybody. But.
Married.
Women you know. I suppose I ought to be.
And the chair How much do you.
When the OR or.
The
role of
the of
the of.
I need under the. I could pay it back
and. That's all right it's crossed.
Thank you property on.
Company on just one.
Thank you very much. For the plan how.
Are you going to make
enough money to buy me
a radio at the one thousand stand every
night. I have discovered that even you
wasting money. And I can
never go without. If I had
a great I would put the. Last minimal you
had but the words in your mouth I've been
better off with. The only reason
I've been with you is because I met
a. Person I've stuck to.
The Brink. Now I have.
Been depressed. That's the matter with.
Me You keep blaming me for not buying your
radio and you think that running down
the radio or by radio you have money
this insurance Well I don't want
a radio you want I never touch those that
are not already. But I love that have
a radio made a good salary he gave me
a good. Living in the same
apartment. I didn't spend
a pain. I'm testing and I don't get it
but just getting up if you don't get
a break and I trust them again I don't.
Think you baby it was bad enough to lose
the company because that would trigger
a copy of course cards and he's considered
a great painter now you are
copping to. Getting crazy and.
I still. Well I think
you were thinking when.
I never saw that and so I should.
Just come. Back.
And then do the dishes.
For the next. You remember. I.
Do.
This.
The only. I was I was
looking for things for
a blind Oh well that didn't go into
like radio even I want to know
about them I wouldn't have to do
radio. They did you read this
great rock this murder in Queens a man
killed his wife with the window Wade in
a body in the conscience of the California
it says here and I've read the paper
thank you if you get away with it did
you go to the chair as he showed. I
managed to get
a chance for these detectors. To put
that paper down and do the dishes.
I don't know. You didn't mean what you
said about giving my endings later the
chance man let's find out.
You won't have to
a friend of mine is taking an apartment
in Greenwich Village now living there
record if he's going to happen if you
do it go ahead with the news about the.
Outlaw are you get that the lie I have it
at the heart of Tony Rivera Illustrated
you know this is art and I'm not really.
Work anywhere else. This would be
skew. In sketches on the wall or in there
in that with his Martin sometimes when
he's working on a
magazine. Some people pay
a lot of money for the. You and I the
midnight hour where the bedroom and I have
this way. But the rest of the jump one
hundred. Or there are some things that
Rivera left you're stuck in the basement
they go with the apartment in there and
you listen here we are there because.
I don't like the law paper but I change
the paper I guess alarming is least I
think it happens.
Polls are right the bank solo is like. A
doorbell.
There's a store you've got
a monkey I have that level where you were
throwing around. Brought me up book on
a you're supposed to be an actress
to Shakespeare fab Pete's sake.
Say so I have. You know what
it is more to live like. To
know the pictures for
a long time. Then omitted. Luckily
. I need at least
a thousand dollars ouch we got
em stuff and now but you never.
Seem to get scared when I talk about money
listen baby you're gonna write where
your water is on the hook and can't get
off it can walk out carry it's got away.
Just drop
a hint that his wife might find out about
this is your show last best then blackmail
it's only blackmail baby when you
damn and that's to get caught.
Let him touch at the door down
the cat sick get rid of it.
Oh. Oh.
The gentle bell that you were there.
Got Thanks Ernie didn't think you were
out and it helped as well I rang rang up
Doesn't about middle of the open where.
Wes. Doing all right for
a working girl don't
start that again. Don't
tell me he's under the saga too
bright. They're going to have Johnny.
You have to do it cause Alex
said. Let me Achille Lauro
friend could be. As talented Johnny will
tell you by going to Hollywood I might try
yet when I read in a movie magazine about
a fellow who landed in Hollywood
star broke and cleaned up
a million now experience either
only had was look and he worked in
a drug store or if he worked Johnny didn't
look like you want to start fighting.
She just is no mystery why you're a
movie actor getting ten thousand
a week for flat but I can tell the Persian
girls in the day what do they do I can't
do that you're so clever why
don't you do it I might run
a face I might. Credit
I was brought over some I think it's
a break from all the. Rest are. Oh
you have company personally in China. You
know me boy and come our Jimmy Now I
don't have a friend of mine that's
a car wreck I do miss Ray He's
made us cry and Johnny. Glad to
know us to grow. How to do. She
was to me I actually knew before
somewhere could be
a good game is to go national. I just
don't seem to remember maybe I'm mistaken
could be well address all clear as I
go it's three zero. Zero don't bother
Johnny I wouldn't think it let me go
alone you might get run over by I think.
About it because it's nice to see it
thanks for this guys my life is OK but I.
Thought I was getting. What's the matter
Chris and I don't think I like that young
man she's in love with oh Johnny I know I
know he is really wouldn't be
a friend but there's something
about him that he's crazy about.
With you. Would you like to see my
pictures now come to that because.
You had. So the first time in
my life very happy. I think of
you all the time all I want
to see you be near you.
I know I haven't any right to
ask you this but. If you ever.
Well there must be another man. Just one.
You still see him. I thought that.
Look you see if I was single
if I had no life but you have
a way yes I know but if she did. Well is
something would happen that would make me
free. It would you marry me oh let's not
talk about how do you when I'm worried
about getting
a job living like this it's expensive I
don't like to ask you for anything more
because. They haven't sold any pictures
like this is the don't you have enough
money I have no idea the problem
money has been actors because I had
a cabinet yet everything is poor or contact
knowing the right people that to get an
agent they charge plenty with my club
exactly with Kitty Oh you to all.
Of. A bedroom. It's close because fuel
is making the right impression when
I was needed thousand dollars just to get
a decent work or I was gonna live at
least one other than about milling other
boyfriend job they've got plenty of
room oh no no no no kitty is another
not from Johnny who I know
well get your money somewhere.
And you're done I don't really believe
you're in the room I am kidding I am.
Chris you have here a caveman I
highlight you know like me well as
a limit as I know. I've got to go on the
back and are coming from our new Q.B.
I'll be waiting for you
I'm sorry you have to go.
Bye bye. Don't forget the money OK.
But I.
Like. It.
I don't get it it was that was
the it didn't make the. Imagine
any one player Malik other than.
Say are you sure he's not
a goalie. He's too dumb to be
a sounding you right there and how do you
get all the money why if he had to work
for a living he could make fifty dollars
a week I just don't know are there been
a but I'm going to find out. I said I like
this one. Where would you find flowers
like that. I wonder if I could sell
and what do I do when they are
and you put them in there are you know
you're going to protect you can leave
valuable paintings lying around with nobody
can thank them or you get in trouble
any GARRETT No his word. He tried
to kiss me today. And don't think I
like this right you've been
to. Me not even sometime
doesn't matter I don't know I'm not there
I think I'm baby John I can't stand to
have anybody touch me but you I hate him
when he looks at me like that they want me
you know dishes or be bought me out of
something I like him better. Love me or you
don't get and what I mean no.
Now. How.
Regulated that was thrust. At
the
desk occupied. When
you're. This is probably
because. It's.
The
new. Thank
you good. Back to
the
of.
Well you got. Some of the painted
those get the Gray thank you.
Hey what's the matter with you will make
you pick him up over watching this. As
well as long as rebelling junk like that
for the price of the can seize when
painted by the village along here. That's
my God shop and this and that snake is
from the Bronx Brooklyn
famous name like. They've got
a bunch of stuff before you know respray
name on it that was jewelry bring me some
more of that we can do business Johnny
thank this jump back to Washington Square
where you got.
The and.
The
of. The
AS. I can see you got
an eye for art that's one of my
best. And some of the things.
Oh I didn't know you were
in Spain too I left.
The they had
a good well they've got some. It's Junior
the something the perspective is that
a bright I should say do look at
my being. With you. And I want to
sell or you want me to delimit I must
you think it was I always thought the
reasoning and when you buy
it then you know it's
a hard business selling which is people
don't buy art now with. No appreciation for
taste no perception and
no perspective he said.
Let me have your name and
address I'll come back later.
And I have and. Without that.
Neck. My reading in I want to get
done in Costa Ricans can AND hundred
others but you type down.
You can tell me what
a dope the old guy is maybe you know the
dope. He turned his painting there with
a lot of money and to check up honest I
was wrong as there with just going to the
peace as with Rush you're
crazy. If I were to gentleman
the good of the earth when
I don't tell me I'm crazy.
I don't know the old boy to
follow his money isn't funny and
a good borrowed or have
a stashed away or even steal it Christiane
keypress Johnny he's not the type you
wouldn't have never met the money didn't
get as the most actress maybe down but not
about art and he took me to museum explain
how everything was then you should have
heard of people still around
and. Want to use the I'm
a metropolitan yank I've
got Thank you very well
a million bucks. Are you
going to. I'm going to
make a monkey or you
lazy legs you can take
a picture to the museum
who says I can. See
where. The day went Jim why don't you
go with the tape we keep in our critic
the best part of the New York mother act.
He took one look and bought the book I
couldn't even give him my picture is not
for nothing you want to get hold of told
me to tell the police you. Don't know.
I suggest
a quest of ballet you. We're going to make
a. Killing So you gave
away two pictures break up
a lot of the night you can
collect the die hard drive.
Now I'm going to tell Chris he will buy
that head he won't that Janeway is
a critic he writes for the new paint our
colleague Alice and I thought I told you
not to do it you're just nervous the all
girl is all of those now me. That's right
I think you know this. Chris.
Because. Go ahead still it is.
I beg your pardon but we're looking for
a man and I'm afraid I don't know and
I'm afraid I can't help you. I'm sorry.
There. These are. All there.
Why did you run away from me like that.
Fifty dollars less twenty percent I don't
know what you're talking about with the
pictures you brought me but that's about
introduce now my name is Jane with the whole
how do you do what is it Joe want when
I can find
a man in the picture you don't know could
do no no that's what we're here for look
if you're
a friend of the painter your partner so
that won't touch with him Why do you buy
those pictures if you don't know who
painted them because they're good.
Don't you know oh don't be so bad it
just got me events she made me promise
not to tell that's what I meant
I like I didn't know. She is
funny about a thing never let anyone
in here that knew put a name on
a picture so I have heard your own
extraordinary artist now she can't there for
anybody to talk about if you
get the idea just wanted
a good that's what I'd like those
do to you're going to give
a catheter I know they were good. Now I
think that Manning I never would have
guessed it was a woman nor I just work a
very strong with my maybe some more of
a show. Earlier.
You're crazy to try things like this tactic
I thought they were kept I know what
I'm doing they don't offer nothing to
cancel my critic always wanted to be an
actress now I should chance you've been
around the old boy long enough to pick up
and lingo P.J.
Ways and when I have them in
here along with the well.
How long has she been
painting ever since she was
a kid Mr De Lay no one died or did you know
she just picked it up and I guess that
the only one I've been encouraging
is going to happen or allow as
a friend you know just
a bit oh I didn't get
your name printed. Jane
she said kind of upset.
Maybe you can talk to.
FLATOW.
Well if. I will know this much.
As well as the pen. Was in it for. Christ
after it built up Mr Prince.
I can usually tell other campuses than
painted by man or woman but you would be
completely mismatch their work
is not only original but as
a masculine force. I was
a take you to paint
a picture. Sometimes And then. Sometimes.
You can tell have to grow
of course. You know how.
I cling I love. That's
a very good way out of every
painting is any good in. A lot of.
These. I can see you're going to be
a very hard case. Why don't you have
confidence in your. Because I can.
Do or I just put
a line around my. Very
stimulating person the doctor
I used to get a little oh. I think
I'm breaking the ice but the dollar
a lot to handle all your work
exclusively is that all right as
a friend that is good you come to the
galleries tomorrow but. Any time it's going
to be about twelve o'clock
the lunch after with me.
She'll be there. I'm glad you're around
the brands to make up my mind for. I can
see you are tired this isn't enough I
want you. To go Until tomorrow thanks and
tell you. Now this is the.
NET now.
They see legs. I don't know
what you told a label to get
a meter right out of your head start was
lunch Well what they don't know if you
know me was that they're like a grave
kid. Let's talk about what he was
a dog about he would talk about I had any
sense I'd walk out on you you haven't got
any sense. Of.
Right here just like you sent
a letter. Come out. Katherine much Gary
the cats say that one bad. KERRY.
CHRIS Oh OK I happen to be
in the next. Alone with the
girl I just loved him at that moment was
here. See I hope you don't my men are
going to debate it I know I'm not God
with Grant but I work that remarkable
painting you have
a little trouble with perspective don't
you that's one thing I never could master
the specter. Well I guess I'll have to run
a lot to God and live up in the earlier
days place about that myself that.
She went you know now by. I don't like how
Johnny's Alright then I thought it was
really as I don't know I don't
like him. Is he the one one what
well you said there was one man I have and
they want you out of I get that I was
you know go ahead and pay if you want to
want to stick around if you're going to
try them.
Today. Oh Katie the I'm going out to
dinner. A kiddie don't be angry why
do you come here if you want to
cry I didn't ask you to come here
please Katie Oh wait God hate
and I can't I can't do
a thing when you're angry with
me. If you want me to go back I
want you to stay here and change.
Chris I'm sorry Chris but why do you try
maybe about something that the been done
with because I. Would you marry me can't
something might happen well you better not
let your wife hear you talking like that
because I'd marry you if you were free but
you're not so let's not talk about it
then you go on like I thank
you. Well I was going to do
this myself but. Hate me Chris.
Being nice to pay.
So I don't know I got over the
butcher shop like a job or do I got
a nice piece of liver. How do
you know I'm Catherine ma. I'm semi.
I don't know what you're talking about how
do you now. And I don't get excited let
me have your reasons the other side of it
doesn't give me that nod Jonica I felt.
Out of you know. I don't know what you're
talking like even coming out roughly
but then you can get those pictures out of
your own page nor the time you were just
talking about the real
ad as they don't get
a rose every day making notes where you
go where generals art gallery in the
distance street and got a window put
a painting like that and Mark.
Talking crazy. To think she's
a genius when you think them down
to something you know now I know.
If you listen to the pink around here I
swear I like that woman. That idea. That
they. Are going to watch.
This just this is. The best thing.
Was and they're right about. That going
to the dinner with them three times
a week and talking about breakfast.
Getting that look in as I gotta do.
What about the wear and tear on my. Apple
will take care of kids. Baby is going to
have a big. And
a shine to. JANET.
Reno. Why.
Haven't my bridges.
How Chris. Don't be angry.
I'm not angry I just can't
understand it's not possible for
me darling I know. How did.
I know. I couldn't you.
Didn't. So how does
how does. That you get
around. Here actually so all
the Jews. I put my name on of. This
don't know him I just couldn't even run
a. Low I can't. Catch.
The pilot. Didn't make it into print
as well the funny part is it made
a great deal of difference. If
I brought those pictures to
a man like Gallery would have
taken them. I'm a failure give
a. Great parent. Most
adults. Don't admit the
Janeway. I am so
well I'm going to keep on saying how
cruel. Don't kid you know I don't cry I'm
happy why just like
a dream this is so good some. Want to make
whose names are no speak just yours are
mine why just like we were
married. I take your name.
Well that gives me the love I around here.
I want to thank you thank you Carrie how
about the come. Up with me.
The new.
The small. Now I
gotta call his cell phone the the
the. The.
The the.
Was the
or are. Or are.
Some Alabama hello there hello Well this
is the first time I've ever agreed with
you Janeway Thank you I find a painter
even more fascinating than a painting such
a life Mona Lisa without the smile something
put. Sometimes it seems as if you were
two people I mentioned that in
my notice if you look at this.
The the.
Lad outside says was to see
who I get a laser is it was
a detective. Use
a detective Well I used to be
Mr cause. I'm sure agonizing.
Quite
a shocker. I'll explain everything
when I was in trouble at
the time and click the links to my speakeasies
on the waterfront or get around the
headquarters. That was up for investigation
when I have now the broken bridge
trying to fix things up then runs in the
speakeasy and says damage is just up the
bridge so I run
a terror Michael jump in where
hope might not come up again. In
my. Trial
it's all out there I am swimming around
the dark and I don't regret what I think
saying I'm all tied up tugboat rests
on right down on top of it. Comes
a call back so I grab
a hold climb aboard and let down my hand
what do you think I got. A pocketbook
that's what I grabbed hold of what I
thought it was or had an inside it twenty
seven hundred dollars and old money made
in anybody commit suicide with that much
money. On a call by John loaded on
a banana boat bounced around there well I
went with that but if you're not there
and I'm not really married where am I.
What's it worth to you for me to
keep my shit just to fade away
yes but if you're at doubts husband wait
a minute I see you needed
there. On the money.
OK Sure it'd be easy for
you to put your hands on
a couple. I I couldn't do
a thing that. You're going back
to or you know. Well enough
to do your favorite Mr
clarinet for adults. And
don't think you're going to get any peace
of mind either I might turn up again some
day I should kick you out
nominate brown man like me.
I'll get you. No use in a minute
what you have to wait here I can get
a Black Berry close to six
o'clock oh wait. A little
a little kitty. Now they get the
champagne baby nice girl you Jenny you
go first. And I does the and I got that I
gets me I give you what that's about the
girl that I. Really.
In
a body I think you've
given back. Oh I. Thank
you.
That's all I get. Event
you're wise with more than.
I want you to get all that's coming to us
it's what about insurance money insurance
in two thousand dollars and your life and
the connectivity it's really yours isn't
. She he said right now
because now I wouldn't touch
a penny of it Mr Higgins but if you took
it would be perfectly legal just her
but I guess that's easy. This is the night
that she always goes out to the movies
and that you even if you take
the money. At it you know.
Why don't you get it that way to be able
to say that I didn't catch it you know and
they're old. Boys you don't.
Show up. There and I can
play sake have. Fun if you come out on
the street and eleven o'clock at night.
Why
. Oh why do.
You.
The an.
OK. A comma like this
is my house spike the
start. Of the neighbors.
Where's the money
in there in the bottom drawer in the
chest when they say give me the hikes.
The old. Listen.
In for. The past.
The hour.
The. Lazy Jeepers are.
The.
Chris.
John is Chris Culliver quick.
With
a push you over on your if I don't know he
was coming here tonight I don't understand
you don't understand anything I want to get
the read I want you to my brains about
I'm tied up with I don't talk like you I
thought it was just that the name That's
right blame it on me I want to keep it
and I don't want to stay just don't talk
like that well it's the truth I'm. Sure.
That's the only thing you ever understood
I'm following.
I.
Thank you. Oh God have mercy upon still
the way it was Summer is my language
oh they haven't been around
a pit of hell all been murdered
to console me and similar
Oh. The Earth.
Now it got to be it in Johnny I thought
a good time is but he
getting tight. For just
a fight less and he can't live without me
any more than I can live without him so
he was coming back here to beat me up she
burst our way that guy shoots off his
mouth. No you don't have to warn me that's
just the way talk you are in love you
understand oh stop it Johnny
wouldn't kill us fly. Back
that's love honey. Ask God but.
How Johnny. Come on Johnny I heard Joe.
And I don't make you very. Much embarrassment
can I help it if I'm in love with
no chestnuts actuation.
On that like Kitty is
evil. It would naturally own
it's not right. I want to be
killed. And that's wrong.
Why did you come here.
To ask you to marry me that your wife had
many wives that's finished I can't thank
you has been turned up
pretty. Don't cry Carrie
I know how you feel but that's all over
now. We don't make mistakes OK what's
happened. I can very well know I want you
to be my wife we will go yeah that's
a far off so you can forget this.
Don't cry cutie please don't cry.
I'm not crying you full I'm laughing.
Oh you're already going on then
OK. I've.
Got
a laugh in your face that is and I first
met you you know don't worry and I'm like
OK thanks thanks for him saying you don't
kill Johnny Five like that you try why do
you break every bone in your body these are
men you don't want to marry me you know
that you can't. Read the book.
Oh. Out jolly good somebody.
One of the. Stand by
the the man the in. Two.
Thousand when
a lump the alpine the
the man than
the now.
Or are.
The
bag.
So under this window. What made
you do it Chris. When these
officers called me I wouldn't believe we
were tipped off on the telephone right
that name taken so I took the case
before you came in. Which is missing.
Over twelve hundred dollars we'll
take him along you can make
a complete middle ground zero on March. I
just can't do it but Mr Holcombe you've
done your duty and I'm obliged to
you. Folks to get on the table take
a longer welcome it's
all gonna help to you.
CHRIS It was
a woman wasn't it. I thought. I'm
not going to put you in jail
Chris. Only of course you're through.
By dollar a day I was not I'm not
a lawyer. Let you take that result drive
try to get away with my girls that was
my. This is your I still
got your initials on it.
But it's her blood. It's forty dollars
taken out of her back about there was my.
Diamond ring right to find
research and analysis. No I
don't because twelve
hundred. Regional. Not
much value but if you ain't around
well I won't know any more you.
Listen you guys all know I mean listen
I got my right. This belongs the old
Joe It's got your fingerprint China Well
naturally I picked it up how did I know
she was dead I thought
she was asleep but. She
didn't think those pictures crosses the
logs he dated the accused brought me
to pictures he told me Mrs March painted
in my expert opinion there is no doubt
about it she was
a very great artist she told me she was an
artist when she rented the studio he was
with her I didn't like him then and I don't
like him now he was mean when he was
drunk he said he was going to think when
he left my place around two am That's when
I tell him Look I'll tell you kill somebody
so we could talk with my ice pick and
then I heard say hello John everybody hung
up he was there are I when I was down to
talk about him being an artist I never saw
a paint that was one of the peculiar
traits she never let anyone see
a paint I've compared her handwriting with
a signature there's no question if
to cut paint the only company I work
because she is done for them
even from Catlin. My way I mean
my life is correct. I
really can't paint. My
copies were so bad I had to destroy
them to get say he's lying.
How much across. The country they go. For
a job in the morning or with
a legit. Thing. Thank you same thing yeah
I don't like to cover excuses but I say
this one I don't mind if you show Coach
Johnny's business because he testified you
couldn't think nobody because John is
goes except Johnny way shot off his mouth
either the best they can when exactly
goes named for them on our watch the jury
kept track showed him I got off the live
here and have that's probably
circumstantial plenty of. That
a fair trial and there is always
a doubt I suppose you fellows
are going to say it was
a miscarriage of justice and someone is
getting away with murder not me there's no
such thing. Mr KRAUSE nobody gets away
with murder. That don't get him started.
That's his pet theory. I go ahead laugh all
you like but no one escapes punishment
. I think you would have
a little courtroom right in here Judge
Jury and Executioner. I don't get it
from murder never solved anything
I gotta tell you covered like
a trout I'm sorry but I have to mentor
right if I was just moved in here work and
never get out right here in solitary. So
you go right on punishing yourself you
can't get away with it. And that is
make any sense you haven't seen much of
murderers I have Mr Cross. I'd rather have
the judge give me the work in the have
to do it for myself. This is
the time I'd rather switch.
The eleven o'clock.
I don't do it I said I don't want my
religious me the day I have the five I
was the victim and.
The on
the
side. Of. The
poor.
The Chinaman.
You. China.
I am
a baby. Can. China
. Claim.
God. I. Care. Can I.
Act. Surprised you can. There is
a high here with how many suck down
south and now you want to marry me
listen to. One person.
You kill make your own but another
count me. There are thousands.
Who are innocent you are
pure as regarding your is
a matter of no no. He loves me I
fight and I. Know my. X.
Is my nurse you just. HUNT
like the classic rock he can
meet by his hero the cave.
Chaplain. Return to.
The heart as far.
As the.
SOLOMON It's
a right. Turn. To. Keep
our eye on. When.
I. Get up I'm not going to get going up.
At you and I told you to get out of
this but you know the mayor's office.
All told you and on about
a label on. Come on come on.
Or.
Was that right that
a crazy idea to look up people five or
six years ago I got it off with my I was
trying to give you some pop. Want to
be trite and executed No it's not
I was.
Gone.
The alright on
auto
loan
. OLIVIA. Thirlby
Burgos amassed.
A really big project ten thousand
dollars I shouldn't have to buy
a lot of. Room
and read. And.
Write.
And.
The girl.